Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - 2-84-227 to 2-84-268, 1984-02 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-03 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - March 1984 Central magazine (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1984-03 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - 3-84-001 to 3-84-048, 1984-03 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - 3-84-049 to 3-84-100, 1984-03 (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - 3-84-101 to 3-84-141, 1984-03 (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - 3-84-142 to 3-84-185, 1984-03 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - 3-84-186 to 3-84-221, 1984-03 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - 3-84-222 to 3-84-262, 1984-03 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - 3-84-263 to 3-84-306, 1984-03 (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-04 (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - April 1984 Central magazine (Box 315, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1984-04 (Box 315, Folder 7)
  - 4-84-001 to 4-84-048, 1984-04 (Box 315, Folder 8)
  - 4-84-049 to 4-84-113, 1984-04 (Box 316, Folder 1)
  - 4-84-114 to 4-84-163, 1984-04 (Box 316, Folder 2)
  - 4-84-168 to 4-84-215, 1984-04 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - 4-84-216 to 4-84-254, 1984-04 (Box 316, Folder 4)
  - 4-84-255 to 4-84-304, 1984-04 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - 4-84-305 to 4-84-357, 1984-04 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-05 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - May 1984 Central magazine (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1984-05 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - 5-84-001 to 5-84-046, 1984-05 (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - 5-84-047 to 5-84-092, 1984-05 (Box 317, Folder 6)
  - 5-84-093 to 5-84-146, 1984-05 (Box 317, Folder 7)
  - 5-84-147 to 5-84-190, 1984-05 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - 5-84-191 to 5-84-242, 1984-05 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - 5-84-243 to 5-84-279, 1984-05 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - 5-84-281 to 5-84-324, 1984-05 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-06 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - June 1984 Central magazine (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1984-06 (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - 6-84-001 to 6-84-046, 1984-06 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - 6-84-047 to 6-84-072, 1984-06 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - 6-84-073 to 6-84-118, 1984-06 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - 6-84-119 to 6-84-170, 1984-06 (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - 6-84-171 to 6-84-221, 1984-06 (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - 6-84-222 to 6-84-272, 1984-06 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - 6-84-273 to 6-84-335, 1984-06 (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-07 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - July Central magazine (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1984-07 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - 7-84-001 to 7-84-053, 1984-07 (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - 7-84-054 to 7-84-085, 1984-07 (Box 320, Folder 7)
  - 7-84-086 to 7-84-135, 1984-07 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - 7-84-136 to 7-84-190, 1984-07 (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - 7-84-191 to 7-84-240, 1984-07 (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - 7-84-241 to 7-84-293, 1984-07 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-07 (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - August 1984 Central magazine (Box 321, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1984-08 (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - 8-84-001 to 8-84-056, 1984-08 (Box 322, Folder 1)
  - 8-84-057 to 8-84-115, 1984-08 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - 8-84-116 to 8-84-171, 1984-08 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - 8-84-172 to 8-84-218, 1984-08 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-09 (Box 322, Folder 5)
  - September 1984 Central magazine (Box 322, Folder 6)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1984-09 (Box 322, Folder 7)
  - 9-84-001 to 9-84-053, 1984-09 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - 9-84-054 to 9-84-094, 1984-09 (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - 9-84-097 to 9-84-138, 1984-09 (Box 323, Folder 3)
  - 9-84-139 to 9-84-192, 1984-09 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - 9-84-193 to 9-84-236, 1984-09 (Box 323, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - October 1984 Central magazine (Box 324, Folder 2)
  - Slides, memos, and transparencies, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 3)
  - 10-84-000 to 10-84-037, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 4)
  - 10-84-038 to 10-84-088, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - 10-84-089 to 10-84-137, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 6)
  - 10-84-138 to 10-84-186, 1984-10 (Box 324, Folder 7)
  - 10-84-187 to 10-84-235, 1984-10 (Box 325, Folder 1)
  - 10-84-236 to 10-84-289, 1984-10 (Box 325, Folder 2)
  - 10-84-290 to 10-84-329, 1984-10 (Box 325, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-11 (Box 325, Folder 4)
  - November 1984 Central magazine (Box 325, Folder 5)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1984-11 (Box 325, Folder 6)
  - 11-84-000 to 11-84-054, 1984-11 (Box 325, Folder 7)
  - 11-84-055 to 11-84-107, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 1)
  - 11-84-108 to 11-84-160, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 2)
  - 11-84-162 to 11-84-216, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 3)
  - 11-84-217 to 11-84-262, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 4)
  - 11-84-264 to 11-84-306, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 5)
  - 11-84-307 to 11-84-351, 1984-11 (Box 326, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - December 1984 Central magazine (Box 327, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 3)
  - 12-84-000 to 12-84-054, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - 12-84-055 to 12-84-099, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 5)
  - 12-84-100 to 12-84-144, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 6)
  - 12-84-145 to 12-84-191, 1984-12 (Box 327, Folder 7)
  - 12-84-192 to 12-84-423, 1984-12 (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - 12-84-234 to 12-84-269, 1984-12 (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-01 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - January 1985 Central magazine (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1985-01 (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - 1-85-001 to 1-85-051, 1985-01 (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - 1-85-052 to 1-85-106, 1985-01 (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - 1-85-107 to 1-85-147, 1985-01 (Box 328, Folder 8)
  - 1-85-148 to 1-85-201, 1985-01 (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-02 (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - February 1985 Central magazine (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Slides, and transparencies, 1985-02 (Box 329, Folder 4)
  - 2-85-001 to 2-85-042, 1985-02 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - 2-85-043 to 2-85-082, 1985-02 (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - 2-85-083 to 2-85-130, 1985-02 (Box 329, Folder 7)
  - 2-85-131 to 2-85-173, 1985-02 (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - 2-85-174 to 2-85-225, 1985-02 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - 2-85-226 to 2-85-277, 1985-02 (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-03 (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - March 1985 Central magazine (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1985-03 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - 3-85-000 to 3-85-047, 1985-03 (Box 330, Folder 7)
  - 3-85-048 to 3-85-094, 1985-03 (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - 3-85-095 to 3-85-138, 1985-03 (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - 3-85-139 to 3-85-189, 1985-03 (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - 3-85-190 to 3-85-244, 1985-03 (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - 3-85-245 to 3-85-288, 1985-03 (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-04 (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - April 1985 Central magazine (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Slides, and transparencies, and memos, 1985-04 (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - 4-85-001 to 4-85-040, 1985-04 (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - 4-85-041 to 4-85-096, 1985-04 (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - 4-85-097 to 4-85-141, 1985-04 (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - 4-85-142 to 4-85-191, 1985-04 (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - 4-85-192 to 4-85-234, 1985-04 (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - 4-85-235 to 4-85-283, 1985-04 (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - 4-85-284 to 4-85-338, 1985-04 (Box 333, Folder 3)
  - 4-85-339 to 4-85-393, 1985-04 (Box 333, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-05 (Box 333, Folder 5)
  - May 1985 Central magazine (Box 333, Folder 6)
  - Slides, memos, and transparencies, 1985-05 (Box 333, Folder 7)
  - 5-85-001 to 5-85-067, 1985-05 (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - 5-85-069 to 5-85-118, 1985-05 (Box 334, Folder 2)
  - 5-85-119 to 5-85-173, 1985-05 (Box 334, Folder 3)
  - 5-85-174 to 5-85-227, 1985-05 (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - 5-85-228 to 5-85-270, 1985-05 (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - 5-85-271 to 5-85-321, 1985-05 (Box 335, Folder 1)
  - 5-85-322 to 5-85-373, 1985-05 (Box 335, Folder 2)
  - 5-85-374 to 5-85-409, 1985-05 (Box 335, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-06 (Box 335, Folder 4)
  - May 1985 Central magazine (Box 335, Folder 5)
  - Slides, memo, and transparencies, 1985-06 (Box 335, Folder 6)
  - 6-85-001 to 6-85-051, 1985-06 (Box 335, Folder 7)
  - 6-85-052 to 6-85-110, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 1)
  - 6-85-111 to 6-85-154, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 2)
  - 6-85-155 to 6-85-204, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - 6-85-205 to 6-85-255, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 4)
  - 6-85-256 to 6-85-284, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 5)
  - 6-85-285 to 6-85-320, 1985-06 (Box 336, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, and Desert, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - July 1985 Central magazine, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 3)
  - 7-85-001 to 7-85-044, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - 7-85-046 to 7-85-093, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - 07-85-094 to 7-85-138, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 6)
  - 07-85-138 to 07-85-175, 1985-07 (Box 337, Folder 7)
  - 7-85-177 to 7-85-211, 1985-07 (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - 7-85-213 to 7-85-237, 1985-07 (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-08 (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - August 1985 Central magazine (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1985-08 (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - 8-85-001 to 8-85-049, 1985-08 (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - 8-85-050 to 8-85-102, 1985-08 (Box 338, Folder 7)
  - 8-85-103 to 8-85-147, 1985-08 (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - 8-85-149 to 8-85-186, 1985-08 (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - 8-85-187 to 8-85-218, 1985-08 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - 8-85-219 to 8-85-246, 1985-08 (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1985-09 (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - September 1985 Central magazine (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1985-09 (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - 9-85-001 to 9-85-045, 1985-09 (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - 9-85-046 to 9-85-085, 1985-09 (Box 339, Folder 8)
  - 9-85-086 to 9-85-130, 1985-09 (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - 9-85-131 to 9-85-178, 1985-09 (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - 9-85-179 to 9-85-214, 1985-09 (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - 9-85-215 to 9-85-262, 1985-09 (Box 340, Folder 4)
  - Clippings: South, North, and Desert, 1985-10 (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - October 1985 Central magazine (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1985-10 (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - 10-85-001 to 10-85-044, 1985-10 (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - 10-85-046 to 10-85-091, 1985-10 (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - 10-85-092 to 10-85-134, 1985-10 (Box 341, Folder 3)
  - 10-85-135 to 10-85-180, 1985-10 (Box 341, Folder 4)
  - 10-85-181 to 10-85-210, 1985-10 (Box 341, Folder 5)
  - 10-85-211 to 10-85-253, 1985-10 (Box 342, Folder 1)
  - 10-85-254 to 10-85-300, 1985-10 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - 10-85-301 to 10-85-342, 1985-10 (Box 342, Folder 3)
  - 10-85-343 to 10-85-375, 1985-10 (Box 342, Folder 4)
  - 10-85-376 to 10-85-410, 1985-10 (Box 342, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: North, South, and Desert, 1985-11 (Box 342, Folder 6)
  - November 1985 Central magazine (Box 342, Folder 7)
  - Slides, and transparencies, 1985-11 (Box 342, Folder 8)
  - 11-85-001 to 11-85-040, 1985-11 (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - 11-85-041 to 11-85-080, 1985-11 (Box 343, Folder 2)
  - 11-85-081 to 11-85-120, 1985-11 (Box 343, Folder 3)
  - 11-85-122 to 11-85-180, 1985-11 (Box 343, Folder 4)
  - 11-85-181 to 11-85-230, 1985-11 (Box 343, Folder 5)
  - 11-85-231 to 11-85-271, 1985-11 (Box 344, Folder 1)
  - 11-85-272 to 11-85-310, 1985-11 (Box 344, Folder 2)
  - 11-85-311 to 11-85-356, 1985-11 (Box 344, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: South, North, and Desert, 1985-12 (Box 344, Folder 4)
  - December 1985 Central magazine (Box 344, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1985-12 (Box 344, Folder 6)
  - 12-85-001 to 12-85-051, 1985-12 (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - 12-85-052 to 12-85-100, 1985-12 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - 12-85-101 to 12-85-151, 1985-12 (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - 12-85-152 to 12-85-199, 1985-12 (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - 12-85-200 to 12-85-253, 1985-12 (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-01 (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - January 1986 Central magazine (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1986-01 (Box 345, Folder 7)
  - 01-86-001 to 01-86-070, 1986-01 (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - 01-86-071 to 01-86-126, 1986-01 (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - 1-86-127 to 1-86-160, 1986-01 (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - 1-86-161 to 1-86-218, 1986-01 (Box 346, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-02 (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - February 1986 Central magazine (Box 346, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1986-02 (Box 346, Folder 7)
  - 2-86-001 to 2-86-053, 1986-02 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - 2-86-054 to 2-86-101, 1986-02 (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - 2-86-102 to 2-85-150, 1986-02 (Box 347, Folder 3)
  - 2-86-151 to 2-86-185, 1986-02 (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - 2-86-186 to 2-86-231, 1986-02 (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - March 1986 Central magazine (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - 3-86-001 to 3-86-050, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - 3-86-051 to 3-86-102, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - 3-86-103 to 3-86-151, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - 3-86-152 to 3-86-200, 1986-03 (Box 348, Folder 7)
  - 3-86-201 to 3-86-240, 1986-03 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - 3-86-241 to 3-86-302, 1986-03 (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Central, 1986-04 (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - April 1986 Central magazine (Box 349, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1986-04 (Box 349, Folder 5)
  - 4-86-001 to 4-86-045, 1986-04 (Box 349, Folder 6)
  - 4-86-046 to 4-86-090, 1986-04 (Box 349, Folder 7)
  - 4-86-091 to 4-86-136, 1986-04 (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - 4-86-137 to 4-86-176, 1986-04 (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - 4-86-177 to 4-86-239, 1986-04 (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - 4-86-240 to 4-86-296, 1986-04 (Box 350, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-05 (Box 350, Folder 5)
  - May 1986 Central magazine (Box 350, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 1)
  - 5-86-001 to 5-86-045, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 2)
  - 5-86-046 to 5-86-092, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 3)
  - 5-86-093 to 5-86-146, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 4)
  - 5-86-147 to 5-86-200, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 5)
  - 5-86-201 to 5-86-240, 1986-05 (Box 351, Folder 6)
  - 5-86-241 to 5-86-290, 1986-05 (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - 5-86-291 to 5-86-344, 1986-05 (Box 352, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-06 (Box 352, Folder 3)
  - June 1986 Central magazine (Box 352, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-06 (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - 6-86-001 to 6-86-045, 1986-06 (Box 352, Folder 6)
  - 6-86-046 to 6-86-088, 1986-06 (Box 352, Folder 7)
  - 6-86-089 to 6-86-135, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 1)
  - 6-86-136 to 6-86-180, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 2)
  - 6-86-181 to 6-86-225, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 3)
  - 6-86-226 to 6-86-279, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 4)
  - 6-86-280 to 6-86-321, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 5)
  - 6-86-322 to 6-86-354, 1986-06 (Box 353, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - July 1986 Central magazine (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - 7-86-001 to 7-86-046, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - 7-86-047 to 7-86-100, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - 7-86-101 to 7-86-145, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - 7-86-146 to 7-86-180, 1986-07 (Box 354, Folder 7)
  - 7-86-181 to 7-86-227, 1986-07 (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - 7-86-228 to 7-86-263, 1986-07 (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-08 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - August 1986 Central magazine (Box 355, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1986-08 (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - 8-86-001 to 8-86-049, 1986-08 (Box 355, Folder 6)
  - 8-86-050 to 8-86-090, 1986-08 (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - 8-86-091 to 8-86-115, 1986-08 (Box 355, Folder 8)
  - 8-86-116 to 8-86-165, 1986-08 (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - 8-86-168 to 8-86-227, 1986-08 (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-09 (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - September 1986 Central magazine (Box 356, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-09 (Box 356, Folder 5)
  - 9-86-001 to 9-86-040, 1986-09 (Box 356, Folder 6)
  - 9-86-041 to 9-86-080, 1986-09 (Box 356, Folder 7)
  - 9-86-081 to 9-86-125, 1986-09 (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - 9-86-126 to 9-86-170, 1986-09 (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - 9-86-171 to 9-86-210, 1986-09 (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - 9-86-211 to 9-86-240, 1986-09 (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - 9-86-241 to 9-86-289, 1986-09 (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-10 (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - October 1986 Central magazine (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - 10-86-001 to 10-86-045, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - 10-86-046 to 10-86-090, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - 10-86-091 to 10-86-140, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 4)
  - 10-86-141 to 10-86-191, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - 10-86-192 to 10-86-245, 1986-10 (Box 358, Folder 6)
  - 10-86-246 to 10-86-297, 1986-10 (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - 10-86-298 to 10-86-327, 1986-10 (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - 10-86-328 to 10-86-368, 1986-10 (Box 359, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: South, North, and Desert, 1986-10 (Box 359, Folder 4)
  - November 1986 Central magazine (Box 359, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-11 (Box 359, Folder 6)
  - 11-86-001 to 11-86-045, 1986-11 (Box 359, Folder 7)
  - 11-86-046 to 11-86-080, 1986-11 (Box 359, Folder 8)
  - 11-86-081 to 11-86-120, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 1)
  - 11-86-121 to 11-86-160, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 2)
  - 11-86-161 to 11-86-205, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - 11-86-206 to 11-86-245, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 4)
  - 11-86-246 to 11-86-289, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - 11-86-290 to 11-86-310, 1986-11 (Box 360, Folder 6)
  - 11-86-311 to 11-86-356, 1986-11 (Box 361, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1986-12 (Box 361, Folder 2)
  - December 1986 Central magazine (Box 361, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1986-12 (Box 361, Folder 4)
  - 12-86-001 to 12-86-045, 1986-12 (Box 361, Folder 5)
  - 12-86-046 to 12-86-100, 1986-12 (Box 361, Folder 6)
  - 12-86-101 to 12-86-150, 1986-12 (Box 361, Folder 7)
  - 12-86-151 to 12-86-190, 1986-12 (Box 362, Folder 1)
  - 12-86-191 to 12-86-235, 1986-12 (Box 362, Folder 2)
  - 12-86-236 to 12-86-293, 1986-12 (Box 362, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1987-01 (Box 362, Folder 4)
  - January 1987 Central magazine (Box 362, Folder 5)
  - 1-87-001 to 1-87-052, 1987-01 (Box 362, Folder 6)
  - 1-87-053 to 1-87-123, 1987-01 (Box 362, Folder 7)
  - 1-87-124 to 1-87-186, 1987-01 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-01 (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - February1987 Central magazine (Box 363, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1987-02 (Box 363, Folder 4)
  - 2-87-001 to 2-87-049, 1987-02 (Box 363, Folder 5)
  - 2-87-050 to 2-87-100, 1987-02 (Box 363, Folder 6)
  - 2-87-101 to 2-87-150, 1987-02 (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - 2-87-151 to 2-87-200, 1987-02 (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - 2-87-201 to 2-87-248, 1987-02 (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, North, South, and Desert, 1987-03 (Box 364, Folder 3)
  - March 1987 Central magazine (Box 364, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-03 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - 3-87-001 to 3-87-045, 1987-03 (Box 364, Folder 6)
  - 3-87-046 to 3-87-093, 1987-03 (Box 364, Folder 7)
  - 3-87-094 to 3-87-150, 1987-03 (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - 3-87-151 to 3-87-195, 1987-03 (Box 365, Folder 2)
  - 3-87-196 to 3-87-250, 1987-03 (Box 365, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-04 (Box 365, Folder 4)
  - April 1987 Central magazine (Box 365, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1987-04 (Box 365, Folder 6)
  - 4-87-001 to 4-87-039, 1987-04 (Box 365, Folder 7)
  - 4-87-040 to 4-87-085, 1987-04 (Box 366, Folder 1)
  - 4-87-086 to 4-87-140, 1987-04 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - 4-87-141 to 4-87-185, 1987-04 (Box 366, Folder 3)
  - 4-87-186 to 4-86-240, 1987-04 (Box 366, Folder 4)
  - 4-87-241 to 4-87-290, 1987-04 (Box 366, Folder 5)
  - 4-87-291 to 4-87-337, 1987-04 (Box 367, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-05 (Box 367, Folder 2)
  - May 1987 Central magazine (Box 367, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-05 (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - 5-87-001 to 5-87-050, 1987-05 (Box 367, Folder 5)
  - 5-87-051 to 5-87-105, 1987-05 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - 5-87-106 to 5-87-155, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 1)
  - 5-87-156 to 5-87-207, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 2)
  - 5-87-208 to 5-87-250, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 3)
  - 5-87-251 to 5-87-290, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 4)
  - 5-87-291 to 5-87-340, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 5)
  - 5-87-341 to 5-87-378, 1987-05 (Box 368, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 1)
  - June 1987 Central magazine (Box 369, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 3)
  - 6-87-001 to 6-87-040, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 4)
  - 6-87-041 to 6-87-090, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 5)
  - 6-87-091 to 6-87-139, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 6)
  - 6-87-140 to 6-87-181, 1987-06 (Box 369, Folder 7)
  - 6-87-182 to 6-87-229, 1987-06 (Box 370, Folder 1)
  - 6-87-230 to 6-87-288, 1987-06 (Box 370, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-07 (Box 370, Folder 3)
  - July 1987 Central magazine (Box 370, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-07 (Box 370, Folder 5)
  - 7-87-001 to 7-87-049, 1987-07 (Box 370, Folder 6)
  - 7-87-050 to 7-87-090, 1987-07 (Box 370, Folder 7)
  - 7-87-091 to 7-87-135, 1987-07 (Box 371, Folder 1)
  - 7-87-136 to 7-87-185, 1987-07 (Box 371, Folder 2)
  - 7-87-186 to 7-87-246, 1987-07 (Box 371, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-08 (Box 371, Folder 4)
  - August 1987 Central magazine (Box 371, Folder 5)
  - Slides, transparencies, memos, 1987-08 (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - 8-87-001 to 8-87-049, 1987-08 (Box 371, Folder 7)
  - 8-87-050 to 8-87-090, 1987-08 (Box 372, Folder 1)
  - 8-87-091 to 8-87-130, 1987-08 (Box 372, Folder 2)
  - 8-87-131 to 8-87-165, 1987-08 (Box 372, Folder 3)
  - 8-87-166 to 8-87-204, 1987-08 (Box 372, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-09 (Box 372, Folder 5)
  - September 1987 Central magazine (Box 372, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, memo, 1987-09 (Box 372, Folder 7)
  - 9-87-001 to 9-87-050, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 1)
  - 9-87-051 to 9-87-105, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 2)
  - 9-87-106 to 9-87-165, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 3)
  - 9-87-166 to 9-87-205, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 4)
  - 9-87-206 to 9-87-242, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-09 (Box 373, Folder 6)
  - October 1987 Central magazine (Box 374, Folder 1)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-10 (Box 374, Folder 2)
  - 10-87-001 to 10-87-050, 1987-10 (Box 374, Folder 3)
  - 10-87-051 to 10-87-115, 1987-10 (Box 374, Folder 4)
  - 10-87-116 to 10-87-169, 1987-10 (Box 374, Folder 5)
  - 10-87-170 to 10-87-195, 1987-10 (Box 374, Folder 6)
  - 10-87-196 to 10-87-250, 1987-10 (Box 375, Folder 1)
  - 10-87-251 to 10-87-305, 1987-10 (Box 375, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-11 (Box 375, Folder 3)
  - November 1987 Central magazine, 1987-11 (Box 375, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-11 (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - 11-87-001 to 11-87-050, 1987-11 (Box 375, Folder 6)
  - 11-87-051 to 11-87-100, 1987-11 (Box 375, Folder 7)
  - 11-87-101 to 11-87-141, 1987-11 (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - 11-87-142 to 11-87-190, 1987-11 (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - 11-87-191 to 11-87-250, 1987-11 (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - 11-87-251 to 11-87-295, 1987-11 (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1987-12 (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - December 1987 Central magazine (Box 376, Folder 6)